

P Ecuador, Guayaquil

isaiasponce-12@hotmail.es

+593 96 891 3869

emilioPonceAlvarado16

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FormatMaker

DEVELOPER AT FORMATMAKER

Ecuador, Guayaquil 08/2021 - Currently (9 months)

- My first and failed startup, Learn Startup Scrum, React.js, Next.js, React.js, Next.js, AWS
 (Apigateway, cognito, lambda), html/css/js, Bootstrap. Online service that allows users
 to edit documents with less effort.
- All the good stuffs.

HUAWEI

Ecuador, Guayaquil 01/2021 - 08/2021 (7 months)

INTERN IN APPLICATION/SOFTWARE DEPARTMENT

- Fix **Fontend/backend Software** of client site in less than 2 days.
- Technologies: postman, html/css/js, /PLSQL, java Prime faces
- Test with clients: 25 modules in one week
- Scrum Management
- Make our client ("CLARO Ecuador") happy by 100% by doing our hard work.

Fermín Rojas

Ecuador, Guayaquil

COMMUNITY WORK - INTERNSHIP - NETWORKING

01/2019 - 05/2020 (6 months)

- Network topology design.
- Configuration of TPlink routers (Network addresses, DHCP, etc.)
- On-site installation.

G2C Integradores

Ecuador, Guayaquil

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

01/2019 - 01/2021 (2 years)

- Reduce money cost by 300% by improving the logic of their serverless functions (Python3, nodejs)
- Develop business Logic and improving their sales by 200%
- Developed frontend for clients, React.js, html/css/js, Java Prime faces
- Database management MySQL, Dynamodb
- Coaching the new member.

CERTIFICATIONS

Google IT Automation with Python (Professional Certificate)

Google IT Support Professional Certificate

Automating Real-World Tasks with Python

Configuration Management and the Cloud

EDUCATION

ESPOL University

Ecuador, Guayaquil

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

TECHNICAL BACHELOR

- Major in Software Engineering and Telecomunication
- Project Thesis: Traceability of agricultural products using blockchain (Python, flask, html/css/js)

High School "Domingo Comin"

Ecuador, Guayaquil



ABOUT ME

Age: 25 years old | Date of Birth: June 1, 1997 Ecuadorian willing to relocate. Developer with more than 2 years of experience in remote jobs. Implementing CI/CD using agile methodologies (SCRUM, XP)

US tourist VISA: Yes
US Green Card Visa: No
Telegram: https://t.me/ieponce

Whatsapp:

https://wa.me/+593968913869

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/isaias-ponce-569109104/

LANGUAGES

English • upper intermediate (B2 Cambridge Certificate) **Spanish** • Native Speaker

SKILLS

- Web Development
- React.js,Next.js
- html/css/boostrap
- Python, Java, javascript, C
- AWS(lambda,api gateway,dynamoDB, S3, cognito, amplify)
- Database Management
- SCRUM and XP
- Empathy
- Tools: VScode, Git, Linux, Postman, Pycharm



https://www.isaias.poncealvarado.com/

ALL MY MAJOR PROJECTS ARE HERE IN MY PORTFOLIO WEBSITE.

Free Wordcloud Generator React.js, Next.js, Html/css/Boostrap, Google Analytics

Free Wordcloud online is a free, open-source Web app that converts text into a wordcloud image, user friendly and responsive UI. (Check the link in My Portfolio)

IQoption Bot for binary trading

Python, IQoption API

In My Github Repo - This is not intended to earn money, just educational purpose

Traceability of Agricultural Products using Blockchain

Python, flas

IMPLEMENTING RASPBERRYPI NODES, WHICH ARE RUNNING PYTHON CODE AND MAKING THE COMPLETE PROCESS OF BLOCKCHAIN WITH DATA SENSORS IN LOCAL NETWORK VIA WIFI (CHECK THE LINK IN MY PORTFOLIO)